A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976, RG 3 FA094
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976; 3; 636.07 Cubic Feet 1659 containers - 1591 letter document boxes, 66 legal document boxes, 1 legal tall box, and 1 half-letter box.
  - Conservation, 1962-1976; 9; 114.95 Cubic Feet 290 letter document boxes, 9 legal document boxes and 1 legal tall box
    - New York State, 7
      - State Council of Parks - New York City Park Commission - A-Z (Box 376, Folder 5, Box 377, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - New York City Park Commission - Blum, 1967-1969 (Box 377, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - New York City Park Commission - Brooklyn Navy Yard, 1967-1968 (Box 377, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - New York City Park Commission - Bussing, 1967-1969 (Box 377, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - New York City Park Commission - Budget/Finances, 1968-1970 (Box 377, Folder 5)
      - State Council of Parks - New York City Park Commission - Roberto Clemente State Park, 1974 (Box 377, Folder 6)
      - State Council of Parks - New York City Park Commission - Clippings, 1967-1978 (Box 377, Folder 7)
      - State Council of Parks - New York City Park Commission - Fort Totten, 1967-1970 (Box 378, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - New York City Park Commission - Harlem River Bronx Park, 1966-1970 (Box 378, Folder 2-4, Box 379, Folder 1-4)
      - State Council of Parks - New York City Park Commission - Harlem River Bronx Park - Groundbreaking and Public Relations Material, 1968-1971 (Box 378, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - New York City Park Commission - Mrs. Lyndon B. Johnson Discover America Trip, 1968 May 17-19 (Box 380, Folder 1-2)
      - State Council of Parks - New York City Park Commission - Members, 1967-1973 (Box 380, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - New York City Park Commission - Memoranda, 1966-1971 (Box 380, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - New York City Park Commission - Moses, Robert, 1966-1968 (Box 380, Folder 5)
      - State Council of Parks - New York City Park Commission - Printed Material, 1967 (Box 381, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - New York City Park Commission - Releases, 1968-1973 (Box 381, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - New York City Park Commission - Reports, 1968-1973 (Box 381, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - New York City Park Commission - Riverbank Park, 1967-1973 (Box 381, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - New York City Park Commission - Staten Island, 1967-1972 (Box 381, Folder 5)
      - State Council of Parks - Niagara Frontier State Park Commission - A-K (Box 382, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Niagara Frontier State Park Commission - L-Z (Box 382, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - Niagara Frontier State Park Commission - Buckhorn Island - Niagara International Music Festival, 1963-1964 (Box 382, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - Niagara Frontier State Park Commission - Meetings/Minutes, 1971-1974 (Box 383, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Niagara Frontier State Park Commission - Niagara Falls, 1964-1967 (Box 383, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - A-C (Box 383, Folder 3-4)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - D-N (Box 384, Folder 1-4)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - N-S (Box 385, Folder 1-5)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - T-Z (Box 386, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Annual Reports, 1963-1977 (Box 386, Folder 2-3)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Bear Mountain (and Inn), 1964-1973 (Box 387, Folder 1-2)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Boys Scouts of America - N. Bergen, 1962-1964 (Box 387, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Budget, 1963-1969 (Box 387, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Budget/Finance, 1971-1976 (Box 388, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Buses/Bussing, 1962-1970 (Box 388, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Clippings, 1963-1976 (Box 388, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Columbia University/Lamont Lab, 1963-1967 (Box 389, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Commissioner Appointments - A-Z, 1963-1976 (Box 389, Folder 2-3)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Consolidated Edison (Box 389, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Consolidated Edison - General Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 390, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Consolidated Edison - Power Plan - Cornwall, NY, 1964-1969 (Box 390, Folder 2-4)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Consolidated Edison - Briefs, 1964-1970 (Box 391, Folder 1-2)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Consolidated Edison - Clippings, 1964-1970 (Box 391, Folder 3, Box 392, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Consolidated Edison - Rehearing, 1969-1971 (Box 392, Folder 2-3, Box 393, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Consolidated Edison - Wirth, Conrad L. - Statement, 1968-1970 (Box 393, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Contributions - LSR, 1964-1975 (Box 393, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Consolidated Edison - Scenic Hudson Preservation Conference, 1964-1970 (Box 394, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Empire State Music Festival, 1962-1963 (Box 394, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Employees, 1964-1976 (Box 394, Folder 3)
        Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2045
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Employees - Nash Castro, 1969-1975 (Box 394, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Employees - Kenneth A. Morgan, 1965-1969 (Box 394, Folder 5)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Finances, 1964-1971 (Box 395, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Fort Lee - Sealantic Fund/Marriot, 1953-1970 (Box 395, Folder 2-3, Box 396, Folder 1-2, Box 397, Folder 1-3)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Fort Lee - Historic Park, 1962-1964 (Box 398, Folder 1-4, Box 399, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - High Tor State Park - Beacon, 1962-1966 (Box 399, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - High Tor State Park, 1971-1976 (Box 399, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - High Tor State Park - Huntington Estate, 1963-1967 (Box 399, Folder 4, Box 400, Folder 1-3)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Iona Island, 1962-1975 (Box 401, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Iona Island - A-Z, 1963-1972 (Box 401, Folder 2-3)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Iona Island - Clippings, 1965-1968 (Box 401, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Iona Island - Acquisition, 1965 (Box 402, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Maps (Box 402, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Memos (Box 402, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Minutes-Meetings, 1966-1976 (Box 402, Folder 4, Box 403, Folder 1-2, Box 404, Folder 1-3, Box 405, Box 406)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Open Space Land Acquisition Program, 1962-1964 (Box 403, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Minnewaska State Park (Box 406, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Minnewaska State Park - A-Z, 1964-1974 (Box 407, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Minnewaska State Park - Printed Material, 1968-1969 (Box 407, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Orange & Rockland Utilities, Inc., 1968-1971 (Box 408, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Palisades Improvement Co., 1965-1970 (Box 408, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Parkways, 1962-1971 (Box 408, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Police, 1967-1969 (Box 408, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Printed material, 1963-1974 (Box 408, Folder 5)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Regional Plan Association, 1969 (Box 408, Folder 6)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Releases, 1964-1976 (Box 408, Folder 7)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Reports, 1971-1974 (Box 409, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Rockefeller, Laurance S., 1963-1976 (Box 409, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Sebago Lake, 1962-1963 (Box 409, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Rockland Lake State Park - South, 1970 (Box 409, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Rockland Lake State Park - North, 1963-1970 (Box 410, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Town of Chester, 1962-1963 (Box 410, Folder 2-3)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Wirth, Conrad L., 1964-1974 (Box 410, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Welch (Lake Welch Beach), 1962-1964 (Box 410, Folder 5)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Transportation Surveys, 1962-1965 (Box 411, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - U.S.G. - National Recreation Trails, 1963-1971 (Box 411, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - Saratoga Springs Commission, 1971-1972 (Box 411, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - Meetings/Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 411, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - Taconic State Park Commission, 1963-1972 (Box 411, Folder 5)
      - State Council of Parks - Taconic State Park Commission - "Clermont"/Livingston House, 1963-1965 (Box 412, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Taconic State Park Commission - Croton Trailway (old), 1968-1969 (Box 412, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - Taconic State Park Commission - Fahnestock State Park, 1962-1968 (Box 412, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - Taconic State Park Commission - Hudson Highlands State Park, 1967-1972 (Box 413, Folder 1-2)
      - State Council of Parks - Taconic State Park Commission - Hudson Highlands State Park - Clippings, 1967-1970 (Box 413, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - Taconic State Park Commission - Hudson Highlands State Park - Dedication, 1970 (Box 414, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Taconic State Park Commission - Hudson Highlands State Park - Photos (Box 419, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Taconic State Park Commission - Hudson Highlands State Park - Photographs, 1970 (Box 414, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - Taconic State Park Commission - Hudson River Expressway Park, 1966-1970 (Box 414, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - Taconic State Park Commission - Meetings Minutes, 1967-1975 (Box 414, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - Thousand Island State Park Commission, 1963-1969 (Box 414, Folder 5)
      - State Council of Parks - Thousand Islands State Park Commission - Adirondacks Inspection, 1963 (Box 415, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Thousand Islands State Park Commission - Sackets Harbor, 1964-1966 (Box 415, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - Thousand Islands State Park Commission - Valcour Island (Box 415, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - Bills re. conservation, 1963-1972 (Box 415, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - Breezy Point - Maps (Box 415, Folder 5)
      - State Council of Parks - Breezy Point, 1963 (Box 416, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Breezy Point - Atlantic Improvement Corp., 1963 (Box 416, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - Breezy Point - Clippings, 1963-1967 (Box 416, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - Breezy Point - Committee for a Park at Breezy Point, 1963-1963 (Box 416, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - Breezy Point - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Statement (NY Times), 1963 (Box 416, Folder 5)
      - State Council of Parks - Budget, 1963-1976 (Box 417, Folder 1-3)
      - State Council of Parks - Camping Program, 1969-1971 (Box 418, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Camps - Camp Sites, 1962-1970 (Box 418, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - Commissioner Appointments - General Correspondence, 1962-1975 (Box 418, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - Commissioner Appointments - A-H (Box 418, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - Commissioner Appointments - I-Z (Box 420, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Committee. Appointments, 1963 (Box 420, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - Concessions, 1964-1971 (Box 420, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - Conservation Law, 1962-1972 (Box 421, Folder 1-3)
      - State Council of Parks - Directories, 1972 (Box 421, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - Employees, 1963-1974 (Box 422, Folder 1)
        Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2044
      - State Council of Parks - Employees - Employee Matters A-Z, 1962-1974 (Box 422, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - Employees - Park Management Intern Program, 1965-1968 (Box 422, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - Employees - Summer Hiring Practice, 1968-1971 (Box 422, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - Fiftieth Anniversary, 1972 (Box 423, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Gateway National Recreation Area, 1971 (Box 423, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - Hudson Highland Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 423, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - Leonard L. Huttleston Memorial Award, 1969-1973 (Box 423, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - Hunting, 1965 (Box 423, Folder 5)
      - State Council of Parks - Land Use Conversion Program (Box 423, Folder 6)
      - State Council of Parks - Law Enforcement Procedures (Box 423, Folder 7)
      - State Council of Parks - Land Acquisition Program, 1962-1970 (Box 424, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Maps, 1970 (Box 424, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - Marine Sanitation Systems, 1969-1973 (Box 424, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - Meetings/Minutes, 1963-1971 (Box 425, Folder 1-4, Box 426, Folder 1-3, Box 427)
      - State Council of Parks - Studies of Park Administration (Box 428, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Modern State Park Administration proposal (Box 428, Folder 2-3, Box 429, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Moses, Robert (Box 428, Folder 4, Box 429, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - Moses, Robert - Moses Tribute (Box 429, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - Moses, Robert - Clippings (Box 430, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - Moses, Robert - Speeches - Public comments (Box 430, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - Natural Heritage Trust (Box 430, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Board for Historic Preservation - A-Z (Box 430, Folder 4, Box 431, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Board for Historic Preservation - By-Laws, 1972 (Box 431, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Board for Historic Preservation - Finances, 1973-1974 (Box 431, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Board for Historic Preservation - New York Bicentennial Corporation, 1973-1976 (Box 431, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Board for Historic Preservation - Printed Material, 1973-1976 (Box 431, Folder 5)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Board for Historic Preservation - Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 432, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Department of Parks and Recreation - A-Z, 1972-1975 (Box 432, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Department of Parks and Recreation, 1967-1972 (Box 432, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Department of Parks and Recreation - Finances/Budget, 1966-1971 (Box 432, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Department of Parks and Recreation - Minutes/Meetings, 1970-1972 (Box 433, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Department of Parks and Recreation - Printed Material, 1973-1976 (Box 433, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Department of Parks and Recreation - Reports, 1970-1975 (Box 433, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Department of Public Works, 1963-1967 (Box 433, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust, 1967-1972 (Box 434, Folder 1-3)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - A-C (Box 435, Folder 1-4)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - C-G (Box 436, Folder 1-4)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - H-M (Box 437, Folder 1-4)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - M-N (Box 438, Folder 1-3)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - O-S (Box 439, Folder 1-4)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - T-Z (Box 440, Folder 1-3)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Advisory Committee for the Improvement of Existing Historic Sites - General, 1967-1970 (Box 440, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Advisory Committee for the Improvement of Existing Historic Sites - Reports, 1967-1969 (Box 441, Folder 1-3)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission, 1967-1971 (Box 441, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Appointments, 1966-1970 (Box 442, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Budget/Finances, 1967-1971 (Box 442, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Clippings, 1966-1969 (Box 442, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Con Edison Pump Project, 1968-1972 (Box 442, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Erie Canal, 1971 (Box 443, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Fort La Presentation, 1966-1967 (Box 443, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Fort Totten, 1967-1970 (Box 443, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Fort Wadsworth, 1963-1972 (Box 443, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Glen-Sanders Mansion, 1966-1968 (Box 444, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Herkimer House, 1970 (Box 444, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Historic Lewiston, Inc., 1967-1968 (Box 444, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Hyde Hall, 1967-1971 (Box 444, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - John Jay Homestead, 1967-1969 (Box 444, Folder 5)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Jones, Dr. Louis C., 1967-1971 (Box 445, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Legal, 1966-1971 (Box 445, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Lorenzo, 1967 (Box 445, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Members, 1969-1970 (Box 445, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Olana Preservation, Inc. - re: College, 1967-1970 (Box 445, Folder 5)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Memoranda, 1967-1972 (Box 446, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Olana Preservation, Inc. (Box 446, Folder 2, Box 447, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Mormon Church, 1969 (Box 446, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - National Conference of State Historic Preservation Liaison Officers, 1969-1970 (Box 446, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - New Windsor Cantonment, 1969-1970 (Box 446, Folder 5)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - New York City American Revolution Bicentennial Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 447, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - New York State Department of Education, 1965-1971 (Box 447, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - New York State History Publications Corp., 1967-1969 (Box 447, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Printed Material, 1958-1976 (Box 447, Folder 5, Box 448, Folder 1-4, Box 449, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Reorganization of Council and Regional Members, 1971 (Box 449, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Rockefeller Center, 1968-1970 (Box 449, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Saratoga National Historic Site and Park, 1968-1970 (Box 449, Folder 4-5)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Schuyler Mansion, 1968-1970 (Box 450, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - South Street Maritime Museum, 1967-1970 (Box 450, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - South Street Seaport Museum, 1967-1971 (Box 450, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - "Springside" (Matthew Vassar's Home), 1968 (Box 451, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - U.S. Government - Dept. of Interior - Office of Archeology and Historic Preservation, 1966-1970 (Box 451, Folder 2-3)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Historic Trust - Wing, William G., 1967-1969 (Box 451, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Natural Heritage Trust, 1968-1973 (Box 452, Folder 1)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Natural Heritage Trust - Contributions, 1968-1970 (Box 452, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Parks - New York State Office for Local Government - Natural Beauty Commission, 1967-1968 (Box 452, Folder 3)